Welcome to TrendsAI, the ultimate smart engine for YouTube trend discovery.
Today, we'll see how to find high-potential niches in seconds.
First, we define our niche. Let's explore the "Quantum Computing" ecosystem.
By clicking Discover, the system connects to Google Trends via our custom service to find real-time rising queries.
The AI generates strategic entry points. Unlike generic templates, these are based on live YouTube data.
We can filter by time range and video format to refine our search.
Once we pick a keyword, TrendsAI analyzes actual YouTube videos.
It classifies opportunities as High, Medium, or Emerging based on their viral potential and freshness.
With TrendsAI, you're not just guessing—you're following the data.
Start dominating your niche today.